



Skövde, SE

EDUCATION

PERSONAL

Name Samuel Svensson Birthday July 10, 1995 Nationality Swedish

Languages Swedish, English, (Spanish)

ABOUT ME

I'm a 23 year old Master of Science student that has a passion for creative programming and smart solutions. I've mostly been doing web-development in Javascript but I am always open for opportunities to learn something new. One of my greatest ambitions is to work with 3D-computer graphics and image processing combined with challenging programming assignments!

CONTACT

Mobile +46 725444332

Email samuel.svensson.95@gmail.com

Address Skomakaregatan 9

602 32 Norrköping

LINKS

Portfolio: samuelllsvensson.github.io

Linköping university

Norrköping, SE - Master of science in Media technology 2016-Present Programming, computer graphics, visualization and design.

Kurser i urval: Kurskod: Programming 101 (C++) **TND012** TNMK30 Electronic publishing Object-oriented programmering TNA003 TNM046 Computer Graphics 3D-Computer Graphics TNM061 Communication and user interfaces TNM040 Modelling and simulation TNG022

Västerhöjdsgymnasiet (high school)

2011-2014 - Teknikprogrammet IT, networks and communications.

EXPERIENCE

Linköping university

Norrköping, SE 2017/09-2018/01 - Teaching assistant Assisted younger students in a web development course.

Norrköping, SE Cygni - Student brand manager 2018-Present

I represent Cygni at campus and coordinate events for the students

Summer jobs: Engine & AC assembler, warehouseman 2015-2017

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES / SOFTWARE

JAVASCRIPT/REACT/JQUERY, HTML5, CSS3/BOOTSTRAP, GIT, NPM. MATLAB, ADOBE PHONEGAP, ADOBE-SUITE & OFFICE 365. SOME C++, JAVA, PHP AND C# EXPERIENCE.